<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Articles on MISG XXI - Tecnologia Web</title>
    <link>https://asantana1970.github.io/static_website2/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Articles on MISG XXI - Tecnologia Web</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://asantana1970.github.io/static_website2/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Opportunities for Business</title>
      <link>https://asantana1970.github.io/static_website2/posts/web-opportunities-for-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 13:47:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://asantana1970.github.io/static_website2/posts/web-opportunities-for-business/</guid>
      <description>MARKETING DIGITAL - ESTRATEGIAS Video de Introduccion Marketing Digitital
1. Marketing por email:
Es una forma de llegar al comprador directo enviándole un email a su correo, con las diferentes ofertas o lanzamientos que son enviadas de formas personalizada segun los intereses de cada cliente.
Si una persona llega a la página web de tu negocio, y te da su dirección de correo para que le envíes noticias sobre los productos que vendes, es porque realmente está interesada en tu marca.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Estrategias</title>
      <link>https://asantana1970.github.io/static_website2/post/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://asantana1970.github.io/static_website2/post/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>Video de Introduccion Marketing Digitital
1. Marketing por email:
Es una forma de llegar al comprador directo enviándole un email a su correo, con las diferentes ofertas o lanzamientos que son enviadas de formas personalizada segun los intereses de cada cliente.
Si una persona llega a la página web de tu negocio, y te da su dirección de correo para que le envíes noticias sobre los productos que vendes, es porque realmente está interesada en tu marca.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter VI: Esmeralda</title>
      <link>https://asantana1970.github.io/static_website2/post/chapter-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://asantana1970.github.io/static_website2/post/chapter-6/</guid>
      <description>We are delighted to be able to inform the reader, that during the whole of this scene, Gringoire and his piece had stood firm. His actors, spurred on by him, had not ceased to spout his comedy, and he had not ceased to listen to it. He had made up his mind about the tumult, and was determined to proceed to the end, not giving up the hope of a return of attention on the part of the public.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter V: HISTORIA DE EXITO: NETFLIX</title>
      <link>https://asantana1970.github.io/static_website2/post/chapter-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2017 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://asantana1970.github.io/static_website2/post/chapter-5/</guid>
      <description>YouTube Oficial NETFLIX
La televisión tal y como la teníamos entendida hasta ahora ha cambiado del mismo modo que ha cambiado la manera en la que consumimos contenidos. Todo ello ha hecho que los espectadores hoy en día vean la televisión, en muchos casos, a través de las propias plataformas de las cadenas pero de un modo “a la carta”. Ocurre lo mismo con las series y películas, siendo Nexflix una de las principales plataformas que ha revolucionado este sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter IV: Desventajas</title>
      <link>https://asantana1970.github.io/static_website2/post/chapter-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 11:14:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://asantana1970.github.io/static_website2/post/chapter-4/</guid>
      <description>Entre las desventajas del Marketing Digital tenemos:
1. Hay clientes que no tienen acceso a Internet. Existen personas que no tienen acceso a Internet, lo cual hace que exista cierta limitante entre la publicidad y una cantidad de usuarios, que por falta de un medio no puedan conocer lo nuevo.
2. Dependencia del Internet¡Y puede fallar! En ocasiones el Internet presenta fallas, por lo tanto el usuario puede presentar ciertos inconvenientes y por ende una muy mala experiencia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter III: Monsieur the Cardinal</title>
      <link>https://asantana1970.github.io/static_website2/post/chapter-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 11:13:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://asantana1970.github.io/static_website2/post/chapter-3/</guid>
      <description>Poor Gringoire! the din of all the great double petards of the Saint-Jean, the discharge of twenty arquebuses on supports, the detonation of that famous serpentine of the Tower of Billy, which, during the siege of Paris, on Sunday, the twenty-sixth of September, 1465, killed seven Burgundians at one blow, the explosion of all the powder stored at the gate of the Temple, would have rent his ears less rudely at that solemn and dramatic moment, than these few words, which fell from the lips of the usher, “His eminence, Monseigneur the Cardinal de Bourbon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter II: Pierre Gringoire</title>
      <link>https://asantana1970.github.io/static_website2/post/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://asantana1970.github.io/static_website2/post/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>Nevertheless, as be harangued them, the satisfaction and admiration unanimously excited by his costume were dissipated by his words; and when he reached that untoward conclusion: “As soon as his illustrious eminence, the cardinal, arrives, we will begin,” his voice was drowned in a thunder of hooting.
“Begin instantly! The mystery! the mystery immediately!” shrieked the people. And above all the voices, that of Johannes de Molendino was audible, piercing the uproar like the fife’s derisive serenade: “Commence instantly!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>